## DANIEL BATANOV

#### Junior Full-Stack Developer

**%** 0884044070

batanoff.s@protonmail.com







#### **SUMMARY**

Driven by a fervent passion for coding, I am actively transitioning into a fullstack developer role. I have over three years of work experience as an Architect and OA tester. A rigorous full-time training regimen at SoftUni has honed my proficiency in React. Node, JavaScript, HTML, CSS and noSQL providing me with a solid technical foundation.

#### **PROJECTS**

#### Mini Finance Innovations & github

This responsive platform simulates online banking, offering features such as top-up, friends, transactions, history and more

- Front-end: React, React Router, CSS, HTML
- Backend: Backendless used as backend service
- API: ExchangeRate API for live currency exchange rates
- Design: Ant Design, react-credit-card-2

#### ra-auth-ui - open source project

"Ra-auth-ui" is out of the box authentication layouts, hooks and pipelines to integrate into react-admin library

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Architect

**2021 - 2023** 

#### IPA architecture and more

- Delivered over 10 architectural projects
- Managed three junior architects while working with other teams
- Being the go-to architect for assignments with short deadlines
- Actively coordinating project requirements and issues with engineers in different departments (HVAC, Electrical, Design etc.)
- Selected to be the BIM architect on the team due to my technical
- · Won monthly award for best BIM architect

#### Junior architect

**2018 - 2019** 

Design Art "K&K"

Junior architect

**#** 2017 - 2018

2014 - 2015

# Integra Consult Project **Quality Assurance**

#### Gameloft

- Developed 100+ unique test cases and processes to remove issues for product launches
- Assisted other teams during overtime to resolve major issues
- Consistently giving feedback to the development team

#### ACHIEVEMENTS AND WORKSHOPS

#### SoftUniada2024 Programing Olympiad

- · Top 10 in web projects category
- 16th place in the final stage out of an overall 157 participants



#### Erasmus + "Youthpass"

Tutor of a social and cultural workshop with Dutch attendance



#### Interdisciplinary Student Workshop 2017 Second-best project award

Worked in a team of 8 individuals as a leader to develop an urban project for 7 days

#### **EDUCATION**

Software University Full-stack developer

🛗 01/2023 - Present

University of Architecture, Civil Engineering and Geodesv

Master of Architecture

2014 - 2020

#### High School of Matematics "Baba Tonka"

**Profile Information Technology** 

#### **CERTIFICATES**

**GRADES** 5.81/6.00 in

#### Basics JavaScript

Loops

 Variables · Conditional Statements

# Fundamentals JavaScript

5.73/6.00

- Data Structures-Map, Set Text Processing
- Functions
- Database Basics
- Classes
- Regex

### Advanced JavaScript

- Statements
- Unit Testing
- Nested Arrays DOM and Events
- · Error Handling Prototypes
- · Advanced Functions
- Inheritance

#### **Applications JavaScript**

6.00/6.00

6.00/6.00

6.00/6.00

- HTTP REST Services
- · Architecture and Testing
- Asynchronous operations
  Client Side Rendering Remote Data
  - Routing
- SPA and Authentication
- Modular Applications

## HTML & CSS

- · Box Model & Position
- Flexbox
- · Topography & Forms
- Responsive Design
- Node JS
- 6.00/6.00 Session Authentication
- Express and Templating · MongoDB, mongoose
- · Streams and Utilities
- React
- ongoing Hooks, custom hooks
- JSX syntax
- Components & (HOC)
- · Context and routing
- **SKILLS**

## Tech stack

JavaScript NodeJS Git TypeScript React MongoDB CSS Tailwind SASS Express.js

#### Soft skills

Communication Problem-solving Time management Motivation Teamwork

#### Other skills

3dsMax Photoshop Figma Illustrator

#### LANGUAGES

**English** Proficient



Bulgarian



